learnthat.com 2008-12-18

# Privacy Policy - Learnthat.com - Free web enabled training for computer courses, IT certification exams, business, online tutorials, and others

**Learnthat.com Privacy Policy**

Learnthat.com LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Learnthat.com, Romancetips.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Your contact information is not shared with any third-parties, and is kept private at all times. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. No individual personal information is ever revealed to any third-parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm).

This site contains links to other sites. **Learnthat.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, and message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Specific information is not shared with any parties outside of Learnthat.com LLC, and all information is held in secure databases and areas of our servers.

## Children's Guidelines

Learnthat.com is committed to helping you and your family have a secure, private time while visiting the web. We will:

  1. NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consent
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consent
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consent
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [privacy@learnthat.com](mailto:privacy@learnthat.com)
  2. Send a notice to the mailing list program to take yourself off the list (instructions in your subscription email). If you are confused or do not know how to remove yourself, send email to [privacy@learnthat.com](mailto:privacy@learnthat.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [privacy@learnthat.com](mailto:privacy@learnthat.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  Learnthat.com LLC 12 Westerville Square PMB #323  Westerville, Ohio 43081  privacy@learnthat.com |   |
